messagetoeagle.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy And Cookies Policy | MessageToEagle.com

**MessageToEagle.com** – Please read the following to understand about our privacy and cookies practices.

## **Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to us. By using this site you agree to the use and any dispute over our online privacy practices is governed by this Privacy Notice. This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both users who are simply viewing the Website and users who are also contributors of content, information, and other materials or services on the Website.

Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by MessageToEagle.com and not to information collected by any third-party sites to which MessageToEagle.com may link or information provided to or collected by third-parties through third-party cookies, web beacons, and other third-party technologies served during your visit to the Websites.

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## **What We Collect**

On some pages, you can register to post comments.

The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Email address  
Website URL  
Your IP

You may affirmatively provide MessageToEagle.com with certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) when participating in various activities on the Website.

Your IP is registered when you use the site. Our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit the Website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

## How We Use Information

We do not share the collected information with outside parties. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

MessageToEagle.com uses aggregated information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Website and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends. In addition, We may use “cookies” clear gifs and log file information to deliver content (which may include third party advertisements) specific to your interests, and remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Website.

## **Third-party Advertisers**

MessageToEagle.com allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to them, and MessageToEagle.com cannot control their activities.

## **Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## **Cookies Policy**

To make this site work properly, we sometimes place small data files called cookies on your device. Most big websites do this too.

## **What are cookies?**

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login, language, font size and other display preferences) over a period of time, so you don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another.

**Our cookies help us:**

  * Make our website work as you’d expect
  * Offer you free services/content (thanks to advertising)
  * Improve the speed/security of the site
  * Allow you to share pages with social networks like Facebook
  * Continuously improve our website for you

**We do not use cookies to:**

  * Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)
  * Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)
  * Pass personally identifiable data to third parties

**How to control and delete cookies**

The majority of web browsers accept cookies, but you can usually change the web browser’s settings to refuse new cookies, disable existing ones or simply let you know when new ones are sent to your device . In order to do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “Help”, “Tools” or “Edit” facility).

However, please be aware that, if you refuse or disable cookies, some of the website’s functionality may be lost. In addition, disabling a cookie or category of cookie does not delete the cookie from your browser, you will need to do this yourself from within your browser. If the settings on your software that you are using to view this website (your browser) are adjusted to accept cookies, we take this, and your continued use of our website, to mean that you are fine with this. Should you wish to remove or not use cookies from our site you can learn how to do this below, however doing so will likely mean that our site will not work as you would expect.

If you have any queries in relation to this notice, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**MessageToEagle.com**
